ngcareers.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Ngcareers

## Privacy Policy Ngcareers.com

Ngcareers is Nigeria's Top job search, recruitment and career site. We publish latest jobs and career information for Nigerians. We connect employers and career individuals. Please read our terms of service below if you intend to use our service.  **_What information do we collect_**   
We collect information such as Name, Email, Address, Education details, CV/Resume, Phone Number, Date of Birth etc from you when you register on our site. You may however visit the site anonymously.

**_What do we use your information for?_**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one following ways:  
\- To personalize your experience  
\- To enable employers search for and contact you for positions that match your profile.  
\- To enable you search for and apply for jobs or search jobseekers faster and better.  
\- To send you periodic updates on our services.  
\- To administer a survey or contest on our site.  
\- To improve our customer service (respond to your request easily and faster).

**_How do we protect your information?_**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**_Do we use cookies?_**  
Yes we use cookies to maintain your session on our site and to service you relevant third party ads

**_Do we disclose any information to our outside parties?_**  
We do not sell trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third partes who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
However during the cause of search by employers, information such as your resume, job objective, resume, name and pic will be revealed to employers to enable them choose the best candidate and to contact you.   
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non -personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising and other uses.

**_Third Party Links_**  
Please refer to our disclaimer section at http://www.ngcareers.com/about/disclaimer/

**_Online Privacy Policy Only_** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**_Terms and Conditions_**  
Please refer to our terms and conditions section at http://www.ngcareers.com/terms

**_Your Consent_**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy

**_Changes to our policy_**  
If we decide to change our policy we will post those changes on this page.  
This policy was last modified on 01/08/2011

**_Unsubsription_**  
If at any time you wish to stop receiving our Information/updates/alerts you can unsubcribe by clicking on the unsubcription link in our newsletters or send a request to register@ngcareers.com. You can stop receiving alerts from us by unsubcribing from your profile page or sending a request to register@ngcareers.com

**_Contacting us_**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by clicking HERE
